

Applicant for:

PHP Developer (MySQL, JavaScript)

Starboard Asia Co.,ltd. 6 June 2019

Sách Nguyễn Văn

Main interests: PHP, HTML5

1. What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

2. When will you be able to join a company?

I have 1 year experience as a PHP programmer, I am a freelancer now, I have done some demo projects with Nodejs and I think I want to be a fullstack developer, especially master Javascript. I think that I will have enough knowledge to catch up with the position that the company is recruiting.



Nguyễn Văn Sách

PHP DEVELOPER

CONTACT INFO

- **1** 04/08/1989
- Nam
- **6** 0937.464.945
- Sacachi@gmail.com
- 61/15 Đường Số 2 Khu Đô Thị Vĩnh Lộc, Phường Bình Hưng Hòa, Quận Bình Tân, TP HCM
- i http://fb.com/sach.nguyenvan.75

CAREER GOALS

I want to improve my skills and knowledge to become a master Full Task Developer.

Besides, I am willing to learn new knowledge to constantly develop myself, especially JavaScript Programming Language

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Response

Learning New, Logical Thinking

PHP, OOP

WORDPRESS, PRESTASHOP

English Communication, English Research

GIT, NodeJS

EDUCATION

9/2007 - 11/2011

University of Economics and Law - HCMC National University

Major: Foreign Economic Relations Graduation Classification: Good.

Grade point average: 7.5

2004 - 2007

Senior High School - Hue College of Sciences

Class of Math and Computer Science Graduation Classification: Good.

Grade point average: 8.0

OTHER COURSES

I also equip myself with more knowledge about Photoshop, C #, Swift , Unity, NodeJs 2018

Complete PHP Programming Course in Hue CIT 2016

Complete the basic PHP programming course at Qhonline.edu.vn

2013

WORK EXPERIENCE

11/2018 - Present

Freelancer

Web Developer

I make some Wordpress website for my customer such as:

- http://diaocthanhcong.vn/
- https://thanhngophat.com/
- https://kienthucchuyennganh.com

I make some demo Nodejs project:

- Know how to use some package module: Express, bcryptjs, express-session, express-validator, nunjucks, passport, passport-facebook, passport-local, sequelize, MongoDB...
- https://github.com/sacachi/loginformposgress
- https://github.com/sacachi/loginformposgress

04/2018 - 11/2018

Bamboo Limited Company

SQL, Mysql Server	
Javascipt, Jquery, Ajax	
Symfony, React	
MongoDB, PosgreSQL	

PHP Developer

- Implement the requirements of the interface and features required by Agency from France:
- Fix bug for Wordpress, Prestashop website.
- Write plugin Wordpress
- Create Prestashop's Module
- Use Ajax to add bulk data to Database
- Some typical projects:

http://hotel-admiral.fr

http://pasion.fr

http://pharmaciedumarche-romainville.fr

https://www.miriaform.com

https://cie-bracelet-montre.com

http://www.clubmedjobs.fr

http://pro-plan.fr

06/2017 - 04/2018

IcodeDesign Company

PHP Wordpress Developer

- Build website from PSD file into a responsive HTML website with Perfect Pixcel
- Build Wordpress website from HTML or PSD- Fix website features, Woocommerce
- Some websites have done:

http://mechamconkheo.com

http://reporttravel.info

http://kieubaotien.website/clothing

http://kieubaotien.website/ibgllc

2011 - 2017

Time before become PHP Developer

Others Business

- 2 years experience working at Planning Department at Hoa Sen Group.
- 2 years experience on Marketing Online
- 2 years experience on Website Search Engine Optimize